

Gunjan Rathod Manager (Maint. & Planning)

CONTACT

- +91 93777 28387
- gsrathod@gmail.com
- Ahmedabad, Gujarat

A go-getter, loyal team player and a continuous learner believing no boundaries in knowledge. Fortunate to have range of experience in different while achieving sectors various milestones in a career span of 12+ years. My vision is to achieve a respected position which is an inspiration for the subordinates and make my family and my mentors proud of me.

SKILLS

Communication

Problem Solving

Time Management

Business strategic skills

EXPERIENCE

Arcelor Mittal Nippon Steel India Ltd September 2018 – June 2021 Surat, Gujarat Designation: Deputy Manager- Material Handling

- Planning & Procurement of spares for 24MMTPA Material Handling dept.
- PR preparation, technical evaluation of offers, & PO follow-ups along with QC co-ordination.
- Maintenance of Material Handling equipment(s) as a shift in charge from MMD.
- Special Assignment directly under CEO and Global MH Head to monitor Coal Handling Operations and Facilities at Essar Power Mahan Ltd. and supplying Coal Mines.

Brinda Pharma Technologies Pvt. Ltd. April 2016-October 2017 Ahmedabad, Gujarat Designation: Asst. Manager- Production

- In-Charge of production department for production of Clean Room equipment(s), Laboratory Furniture for the pharmaceutical industry.
- Execution of FATs, Documentation for clients for DQ, IQ, OQ and audit requirements.
- Compliance of equipment(s) for CE, GAMP, GMP, and SOP.
- Representing organization for ISO9001:2015 certification activities to become ISO certified company.

Orient Enterprise Guj. Pvt. Ltd. March 2015-October 2015 Ahmedabad, Gujarat Designation: Technical Service Manager

- Manager of all three branches (Ahmedabad, Rajkot & Haridwar) for the execution of AMCs, and ARCs for Predictive Maintenance services which include Condition Monitoring, Laser Shaft Alignment, Dynamic Balancing, Thermography and Acoustic Emission.
- Problem Solving, Improving Plant and Equipment Reliability at Customer's end.

Gunjan Rathod Manager (Maint. & Planning)

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION:

B.E. in Mechanical Engineering with First Class in 2008 from L. D. College of Engineering, Ahmedabad affiliated to Gujarat University.

KEY STRENGTH:

- Team player, analytical thinking, costconscious and timely turn-around of the job with quality.
- Excellent verbal and written communication skills.
- Flexible and level-headed even under pressure.

PERSONAL INFORMATION:

• Date of Birth: 28/03/1987

• Gender: Male

 Written and Spoken Proficiency in Languages: English, Hindi, Gujarati

• Marital Status: Divorcee

Nationality: Indian

• Passport No: J9171123

Aakash Oil Field Services Ltd. May 2014-Jan 2015 Ahmedabad, Gujarat Designation: O&M Manager

- Operations & Maintenance Manager of Natural Gas Compressor Plant on Contract with O.N.G.C. LTD for GCP-KALOL of Ahmedabad Asset in contract with Dresser-Rand comprising 11 Gas Compressors & utilities.
- Client Communication, Conducting all meetings and Audits by both Govt. authorities (DGMS) as well as internal auditors, HSE activities.

Essar Steel India Ltd July 2008 - April 2013 Surat, Gujarat Designation: Deputy Manager

- O&M of Pump Houses, Clarifiers, Air Compressor
 Station & Cooling Towers as Utilities Shift In-charge.
- Erection and commissioning of utility systems for both Corex C-2000 furnaces for all media lines.
- Erection as well as commissioning of Static and rotary types of equipment, media lines as well as a water system for 3 MTPA Steel Making Plant.
- Maintenance of Blast Furnace Proper, Hydraulics, RMHS, SGP, De-dusting System, Preventive Maintenance.
- Planning and procurement for Blast Furnace Mechanical Maintenance Dept. for faster start-up.